// theOffice.ts

import { Topic } from '.';

export const theOffice: Topic = {
  topic: 'The Office',
  level: 'Intermediate',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 100,
  totalTime: 600,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does Michael pretend to fire Pam over in Season 1?',
      choices: [
        'Stealing Post-It notes',
        'Not answering the phone properly',
        'Being late',
        'Wearing too much makeup',
      ],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Stealing Post-It notes'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the name of the company Ryan sets up that sends messages to all of your devices?',
      choices: ['Wuphf.com', 'PingMe', 'ChatSnap', 'ConnectNet'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Wuphf.com'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Who does Michael hit with his car?',
      choices: ['Meredith', 'Kelly', 'Angela', 'Pam'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Meredith'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'What does Jim put Dwight\'s stapler in?',
      choices: ['Jello', 'Honey', 'Peanut Butter', 'The fridge'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Jello'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is Pam’s favorite flavor of yogurt?',
      choices: ['Mixed Berry', 'Strawberry', 'Vanilla', 'Banana'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Mixed Berry'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of Angela’s cats does Dwight freeze?',
      choices: ['Bandit', 'Sprinkles', 'Princess Lady', 'Mr. Ash'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Sprinkles'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Who starts the fire in the office?',
      choices: ['Ryan', 'Dwight', 'Michael', 'Kevin'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Ryan'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the name of Jan’s candle company?',
      choices: ['Serenity by Jan', 'Jan’s Jams', 'Scent of a Woman', 'Candle Cove'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Serenity by Jan'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'What tattoo is Andy forced to get?',
      choices: ['A Nard Dog', 'A Wolf', 'The Cornell Crest', 'A Baby'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['A Nard Dog'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'What does Michael burn his foot on?',
      choices: ['A George Foreman Grill', 'A Hot Stove', 'A Fireplace', 'A Camping Grill'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['A George Foreman Grill'],
      score: 10,
    }
  ],
}
